

### **SKILLS**

Data Structures and Algorithms ·

JAVA · SpringBoot · Hibernate ·

Javascript · HTML - CSS · SQL ·

Github · DBMS

# **EDUCATION**

# Diploma in Full Stack Web Development

Masai School

2011 Bangalore

### B.B.A

Panipat Institute of Engineering & Technology

12/2021 - 12/2022

### **STRENGTHS**

### **Engaging Personality**

Engaging communicator, can be persuasive, but always listen carefully.

### Patient and Flexible

Aware that the learning curve is different for everyone and adapt to each student.

### **Delivering Results**

Focus on the key inputs and deliver them with the right quality and in a timely fashion.

#### Confident

Dependable and responsible good at communication.

#### Collaberative

A good team player and comfortable working with team

### LANGUAGES

English Proficient ••••

Hindi Native •••••

# PARAS AGHI

# Java Backend Developer

\$\ +919355200021 @ parasaghi@gmail.com \$\@ https://paras-aghi.github.io/

Panipat, Haryana

### **SUMMARY**

To be in a responsible position in an organization, which is career oriented, with opportunities to is my knowledge and experience, leveraging on my strengths, self-confidence, perseverance, commitment and progress to ultimately head the unit with global scale of operations.

### **EXPERIENCE**

# Digital Marketing Intern

05/2019 - 07/2019

Chandigarh

# RethinkUX- Chandigarh

Managed Company's Social Media

- Handled Facebook Ads for clients of RethinkUX
- Learned various concepts in digital marketing including basics of Search Engine
- · Worked in a team.

### India Infoline- IIFL

05/2018 - 08/2018

# Sales and Marketing Intern

Delhi

- · Did prospecting calls to customers
- · Sold Mutual Funds
- · Mentored by an Experienced Manager

### **PROJECTS**

### One-Mg

Location

Git | HTML | JavaScript | CSS

- Used Various Tools like HTML, CSS, Javascript;
- · Created Slideshow on the Home Page;
- Various Templates
- https://github.com/AFFAN-AHMAD/project-1mg

### PluralSight

Git | HTML | JavaScript | CSS

Short summary of your work

- Used Various Tools like HTML,CSS,Javascript
- Created Slideshow on the Home Page;
- Various Templates
- https://github.com/PARAS-AGHI/PLURAL-SIGHT

# **ADDITIONAL SKILLS**

Snooker · Reading · Watching binge